Meet SkillBridge, built to find talent keyword filters miss.
Scan 100K profiles, explore top-K, export official top 100.
JD Intelligence extracts must-haves, disqualifiers, logistics, and culture.
Hybrid scoring blends semantics, career proof, behavior, and penalties.
Candidate details show evidence, weaknesses, trust, and risk flags.
Compare finalists side by side before making recruiter decisions.
Control Room reveals how weight changes shift rankings.
Export guardrails validate the exact challenge submission file.
The PDF deck explains approach, workflow, scoring, and results.
Architecture stays reproducible: React, FastAPI, offline ranker, evidence only.